[SUBARU] So I'll just
get someone to kill me.
[gasp]
It really is
an endless desert.
[sigh]
[boom, scream]
What the hell is that thing?
[crash, yelp]
[creak]
Please no.
[scream, squelch]
[thud]
What the hell?
Come on,
give me a break, will you?
Answer me already,
Subaru Natsuki!
[scream]
Someone!
Someone help me.
Please!
[crackle]
[gasp]
[cough]
[sand hissing]
I'm underneath the desert?
[squelch]
Shit!
Holy shit!
What the hell?
What the hell do
you want from me?
[theme music]
♪ ♪
[pants, echoes]
This would be the third one.
[gulps]
How long has it been?
Three hours now.
Maybe even four.
[panting]
[thud]
Damn it!
[water gurgles]
[thumps]
Screw you!
Why?
Why do you have to
be in my way?
[sobs]
What-- what the?
Damn it.
Stop screwing with me!
Huh?
Right.
All that running.
I ran and ran.
I'm done with it.
Yeah, I'll just kill you.
[laughs]
I have no idea which one of you
it was, but I'll kill you.
I swear I'm going to kill you.
I'll make sure you get
what you deserve.
Kill you, kill you, kill you.
Kill you, kill you,
kill you, kill you,
kill you, kill you, kill you!
Kill you, kill you, kill
you, kill you, kill you.
Kill you, kill you, kill you,
kill you, kill you, kill you!
[pants, cackles]
[gasps]
[retches]
So then Shaula wasn't the one.
Beatrice and Meili are only
kids so they'd be easy.
Emilia seems to trust me.
I could catch her by surprise.
In that sense,
the most dangerous ones
are Ram and Echidna.
And then there's also Julius.
It would save me
a lot of trouble
if he'd just go die on his own.
[sobs]
[gags]
Emilia and Beatrice are the
only ones I haven't seen yet.
One of them
must be responsible.
[crunch, gasp]
Oh, it's you.
[croak]
[groans]
[foreboding music]
♪ ♪
Stop following me around.
I'm busy and I don't have time
to play with you!
I still have to kill the rest.
Anyone who's still alive
needs to die.
If you're going to keep
getting in my way, then fine!
[squelch]
[cackle]
Damn it!
Damn it, damn it, damn it!
What the hell?
What the hell is all this?
Why? What's your deal?
You and all the others
in this damn place,
the corpses of the ones
still breathing,
what the hell's going
through your heads?
What are you trying
to accomplish here?
Let me make this
perfectly clear.
I don't give a shit
about any of you.
From the start,
the only thing you've done
is shove your problems
down my throat!
You're all too
up your own asses
to even consider anyone else.
But what about me?
I've got plenty of my own damn
problems to deal with here.
[sobs]
Why does it have to be me?
Why can't you all
just leave me alone?
I want to be by myself.
Come on.
At least let me have that.
[wails]
[ground rumbles]
[gasp]
[squawk]
What are you doing?
[screams]
[squawk, blood splashes]
[panting]
[gasps] Please, no more.
No, I don't want to die!
[thump, grunt]
Listen!
[thud]
[crumble]
What the hell?
[footsteps]
What do you want?
Who the hell are you?
Next time, I hope
you can figure it out.
Hero.
[splatter, whack]
[EMILIA] Subaru.
Hey, answer me, Subaru.
Are you all right?
Emilia.
Oh, what a relief.
I was really worried about you.
Hm?
Subaru?
[gasp]
Is there something wrong?
He must still be
half asleep, I suppose.
For someone who worries us
as much as you did,
you sure are easygoing.
[squawk]
It's you.
I'm unsatisfied with
this outcome, I suppose.
After all, the ones who
found him lying on the ground
were Emilia and Betty.
[laugh] Now don't sulk.
It's OK.
Subaru and Patrasche
are really close, is all.
Hey, Subaru, you're absolutely
sure you're feeling all right?
Yeah, I'm doing totally fine.
No problemo.
I guess all the exhaustion
just caught up to me.
It's not weird for tired
people to pass out, you know.
Right.
But when you feel tired,
you should tell us, honestly.
It's not good to push
yourself so hard.
[SUBARU] I know
I'm taking a big risk here,
but this time I'm not going to
tell them about my memory loss.
I'm going to find out
if it's connected
to the reason I'm getting
killed over and over again.
Although, frankly,
while I could
see killing someone
over information
you don't want them
to know or remember,
I'm finding it a lot harder
to think of a reason anyone
would kill over something
being forgotten.
[pop]
Huh?
Subaru, you've got that
furrowed brow
on your face again.
What did I even do
to make her get so comfortable
and close with me anyway?
I wasn't able to find either
of their bodies before, but--
[KILLER] Next time,
I hope you can figure it out.
Hero.
[SUBARU] That voice didn't
belong to one of them.
In fact, no one in this
group really sounds--
[RAM] Baresu.
Stop staring into space
and help me fetch some water.
Oh, sure.
Sorry.
I hear you were
sleeping in the archive.
You've got to stop trying
such stupid things.
You'll just cause trouble
for everyone.
You're right.
I'll be careful.
I apologize
for making you worry too.
You think I would be worried?
About what?
- I don't know.
I guess for my safety.
Ha!
Good morning, Master.
You got some quality
Z's last night?
[gasp]
[SHAULA] Oh, me.
I slept like a rock.
Thanks for asking.
I had a dream
about the past, actually.
Yeah, it was you and me
and my mom.
And also--
OK, OK, I get it.
You can tell me
all about it later, OK?
Anyway, did you notice
anything about me
when you saw me this morning?
About this morning's Master?
Like usual, you were sexy AF.
I've waited 400 years
for you to propose.
You've got
the patience of a saint.
If you didn't notice
anything, it's all good.
You sure?
[door clacks]
Huh?
[sigh]
Shaula, I need a favor.
Huh?
What is it?
[squeak]
[SUBARU] Julius.
I want to talk to you about
what happened last night.
Just the two of us, you know.
[JULIUS] About last night?
I assumed that that
conversation was long over.
Do you disagree with that?
Yeah, I sure do.
I wasn't satisfied
with the outcome
of our chat in the slightest.
Satisfied, eh?
I see.
That's very like you.
However, do you not feel
that's a bit too selfish?
You don't seem
to be satisfied
with how it ended either.
Look, we're the same.
Both holding on to something
that pisses us off non-stop.
And you expect me
to just live with it?
Like hell I can.
Well, then,
what other choices
do we have in your mind?
My feelings are exactly what
I conveyed to you last night.
Beyond that,
I have nothing left to say.
Your secret with Ms. Anastasia,
or rather, Echidna,
was one that I was
not trusted to be privy to.
[SUBARU] The secret
between me and Echidna.
You meant no harm in keeping
it from me, I understand.
And I've spoken with Echidna,
though not nearly enough.
I know she can be trusted,
or that there
is no option but to trust her.
If I hope to save
Ms. Anastasia,
then my only option is
to bet on that being true.
And even if getting her back
doesn't mean that
she'll be able to remember
who I am anymore.
What does that mean?
Enough.
I beg you,
please don't make me feel
any more pathetic
in your presence.
When you brought up
what happened last night,
it frightened me a bit.
I didn't know what I would do
if you had ended up
apologizing to me instead.
What do you mean?
Don't think I follow.
If you had, well,
I can't help but wonder
how I would have responded.
However, I'll never know
for sure, I suppose.
[door clacks]
[sighs]
[SHAULA grunts]
You sure you're cool leaving
things like that, Master?
Yeah.
I don't think Julius had
anything to do
with what happened to me
in the archive.
Although now he's even
more suspicious
of who I was yesterday.
Yeah, I don't really get it,
but was I able to be
at least a teeny bit useful?
Yeah, you totally nailed it.
Because I knew I had
you there to support me,
I was able to confront
Julius without any fear.
[giggle] That makes me
so happy to hear.
So if that's the case,
listen, Master.
I deserve a little reward,
don't you think?
And a big hug would be perfect.
Not happening.
[yelp]
You poopyhead meanie jerk!
You told me you'd give me
any reward I wanted,
as long as it wasn't
way out of bounds.
How can you go back
on your word?
I didn't.
You just don't seem to
understand what a boundary is.
[groans]
Come on.
Who's after you?
And what did you do
to put a target on your back
like this, Subaru Natsuki?
I'm not sure
where to go from here.
I'm starting to think
I should go and ask Patrasche.
Huh?
The land dragon, what?
She keeps giving me
the stink eye.
I don't like her.
Hey, stop it.
I won't let you badmouth
Patrasche like that.
Even if it was acceptable
to talk smack about everyone,
I wouldn't let anyone
say a single bad thing
about Patrasche.
Whoa, there, Master.
Just how badly does that
land dragon have you whipped?
On that note, this little
meeting of ours is adjourned.
I'll see you around.
Aah!
So you're just going to leave
without rewarding me?
But that's not enough
to make me lose heart.
I strive to be a woman
of convenience.
In fact, that is my sole
reason for living.
That's a whole lot
to offer someone.
What's so special
about Subaru Natsuki?
Huh?
You OK?
Oh, damn it.
[gasp]
You don't have
to be convenient.
I don't want you
worrying about all that.
It's my bad.
I'm sorry.
Master.
Having you there
was a big help to me.
It's that simple.
Master.
You're finally--
at last you're ready to--
--give me
all your sweet loving!
Hey, boundaries, woman!
[water drips]
What if the way they've all
been acting isn't genuine?
I have no idea
what the heck
I'm supposed to believe
anymore.
[sigh]
Guess the only one I can
really trust is Patrasche then.
Maybe I'd be happier
if I left to live in a paradise
where us two could live
peacefully together.
[MEILI] Uh-oh, I heard that.
[yelps]
[giggle] I get it.
You want to take Patrasche
and run away from here.
If you let Beatrice
and Emilia hear you say that,
they would start
crying for sure.
Oh, come on,
it was just a crappy joke.
Forget you ever heard it,
will you?
Yeah, sure.
You know, even if that
is how you honestly feel,
I won't laugh
at you or anything.
If anyone could understand it,
it's me.
I've lived with mabeasts
all my life, remember?
Yeah, of course, mabeasts.
So kind of like you
were raised by wolves?
[giggle]
You said that yesterday, too.
My mom was incredibly strict.
On top of that, Elsa, who
was with me most of the time,
didn't do very much.
So there was a lot I had to
take care of by myself y'know.
OK, wait, wait, wait.
The more you talk, the more my
brain turns into Swiss cheese.
Look, I'm super busy right now.
Go play with Shaula
or something.
The half-naked girl?
I don't mind doing that, but I
do have some business with you
at the moment.
What business?
[MEILI slurps]
You said something
to me yesterday,
and it got me thinking, how
seriously should I take that?
[eerie tone]
[grunt]
What is this?
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
No, but why?
No way.
It's not.
It can't.
Please Meili.
Hey, Meili!
Meili, Meili!
Damn it.
Damn it, damn it.
No way.
I killed her.
But why would I do that?
[sleeves rustle, gasp]
[hyperventilates]
SUBARU NATSUKI WAS HERE
EMPTY SHELL
[singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪